RITU RANJAN MALLICK

Father's Name: Kharendra Narayan Mallick

D. O. B : 19-03-1999
Nationality : Indian
Religion : Hinduism
Sex : Male
Marital Status : Unmarried

Location : Ahmedabad , Gujarat (India)
E-mail : rmallick1903@gmail.com

Mobile : +91-9831525987

Objective

1.7+ Year Experience in warehouse operation is looking to acquire position with a pace setting and innovative company that will fully utilize lean production management capacity planning material control, and maintained a lower inventory but still meet the slices in the schedule and forecasted demands.

Core Strengths

- Excellent verbal and written communication skill.
- Strong supervisory and leadership skills.
- Ability to anticipate and solve problems.
- Proficient with data entry and inventory software and systems.
- Learn from mistakes.
- Complete all closing duties in an efficient manner.
- Good team member.
- Stock Management.
- Manual Handling
- Health and Safety.
- Customer handling.

Work Experience

1. Warehouse operation support agent -Fedex Express January 2021 to 18th May 2022.

- 2. Executive Warehouse Operation- Apollo Suppy chain (due to transition) 19th may 2022 to june 2022.
- 3. Regional OPS- Senior Associate Paytm

July 2022- Present.

Activity done by me

- Supervising warehouse staff and daily activity. Managing, evaluating and reporting on warehouse productivity.
- Typically basic computer skill included word processing, managing computer files, and creating presentations.
- Advance computer skill include managing databases and running calculations in spreadsheets.
- Responsible for overseeing a wide verity of warehouse activity including receiving goods and dispatch goods and maintaining inventory.
- Interpreting company policy to workers and enforcing safety regulations.

Education

MBA – Distance learning course

IGNOU (Dinabandhu Andrews College) – Kolkata, West Bengal, India

Bachelor of Commerce – Distance learning course

IGNOU (Dinabandhu Andrews College) – Kolkata, West Bengal, India



Higher Secondary	2016
Shree Vishudhanand Saraswati vidyalay- Kolkata, West Bengal, India	
Secondary	2014
Tollygunge Adarsh Hindi High School- Kolkata, West Bengal, India	

Computer Knowledge

Information Technology Application

- Good in Tally ERP-9, GST
- Proficient with Microsoft Excel, and Word.
- Proficient in mail handling.
- Proficient in Sap
- Proficient in NERP.
- Claim process in NERP.

Key Deliverables

- Train, Supervise and evaluate the performance of assigned warehouse employees.
- Assign workloads to warehouse workers. Receive, unpack, pack, load, issue, store and deliver materials.
- Responsible for restocking shelves, accepting incoming orders, processing and packing orders, counting inventory and ensuring orders are shipped in a timely manner.

Languages

Languages	
English : - Very good command on reading, writing and s	peaking.
Hindi: - Excellent and very good command on reading, w	vriting and speaking.
Bengali: - Very good command on reading, and speaking	g.
I hereby declare that the above particulars of fact and my belief and knowledge.	information stated are correct to the best of
Date:	Signature: